Given an array of integers and a target value, determine the number of pairs of array elements that have a difference equal to the target value.

Example
k = 1
arr = [1,2, 3, 4]
There are three values that differ by k = 1: 2 -1 = 1, 3 - 2 = 1, and 4 - 3 = 1. Return 3. 


Function Description
Complete the pairs function below.
pairs has the following parameter(s):
• int k: an integer, the target difference
• int arr[n]: an array of integers


Returns
• int: the number of pairs that satisfy the criterion

